And this is the starting lineup for Diego Martinez and Blasparmas as you mentioned defense has been there a kill is here
Will there be Marmo moving inside to play alongside Alex Sware is the captain at center back
Jenny the last Palmer starting lineup Alex what do you make of Barcelona's starting lineup today most of the changes for
Handsy flick in recent weeks have come in the center back pairing five different center back pairings in the last five games today
It's Kubasi and Eric Garcia
Only did the things to fix what was going wrong for last Palmer's early on and they seem to have turned a corner
But I mentioned the Christmas a new year break
Perhaps coming at the wrong time for last Palmer's because they haven't been the same team since
That's free kick for the visitors
We've gone 12 games on beat now in all competitions since the break it was
Kunde only half away
Only entirely relieving the pressure Maledo picking up the pieces for the home team and then a shot from distance which Shesney is not able to claim and
But Bernie
Was there an offside flag there may have been choice in goal
Yeah, offside the moment that
Budget he takes the shot Mac burr the last Palmer's defense already looking under duress here
It's an ominous start for them in the header over the top on the angle leaning back rather
unlikely move from Sheffield United
It's in in his direction couldn't get a touch on it the follow-up shot is a decent one
Shesney always confident it was asking just why did the goal that
It was a good effort by BT and
This is what you need to do if you're if you're the last Palmer's defender you need to finish the thing producing assists
reading yes
Now that the flags staying down for now, but for how long is the question of Sunday?
And
And gets the shot away Shesney
There's a decent one he turned it behind
You've got the high line of Barcelona. Sandro is coming from behind having a lot of side
But it's sandroll the one who gets the ball. It's a very similar move
Has peeled away into some space Kunde cost to meet him
Here's Alberto Maledo cutting inside getting the shot away
Probably three or four feet wide in the end
Maledo's quality right footer player on the left he will always cut inside and tried to open an angle from shooting
He tried to adjust it to the far post he went wide, but this is yet another
Of course a team that never
A huge amount of money to spend they got some defensive concern here as Barcelona
Time made the most of this Raffinia and they didn't quite do that did he
Basit working the
Corner short the cross eventually arriving. It's a good hook away. Wasn't it my asu go
Facing his own goal, but it breaks kindly here and the shot is on
The medium out may have been a fraction offside
No, it's badger these playing everyone on site
It was not only for him to to try to head it, but also to call the attention of the defenders are clearing this pace for our teammates
It's getting more and more involved. Does not you know now he's found Danny holmo
It's absolutely brilliant
Just like that they slice last Parmas open and Danny holmo
Is ended his own personal gold route in some style
Ability to operating tight spaces and he's the one that started the counter attack La Min Yamaha just
Connecting with him in tight spaces and this
This triple against Alex Bunoz
Just changing the ball from the right to the left
And then smashing in into the crossbar
Nothing to do for Jasper Silicent what a goal. This is
Danny almost quality the ability to receive the ball with one foot to switch it
To the other and he had been able with technically the weaker foot
To send these shots absolutely brilliant by Danny Omo
These it sharp challenge there on Alex Munoz the left back which
For his ignored allowing an advantage to play as a Sandro from distance
Well, they don't Danny Omo just sprinting into space
Providing a platform now for Balda and Rafini out feeding in towards the far post and Yamal got there
But the angle was too tight drolet
Beautifully done by Barcelona beating the high press that last bomb as word Trent
That means you'd have used his right foot
But it's all Barcelona at the moment last Parmas looking fairly ragged all of a sudden the back at Levit Dorsky unable to punish them
For the knockout punch on they 20 minutes to go
They really deserve it and look at the difference with Laminia Malin the first half and in the second half just
paul Barci is also
A part of shabby's plan of injecting more players into the first team
Now Balda is trying to live in Dorsky
Any bank left footed over the top
No, I'm sorry. I don't know. Yeah exactly. Beatty was playing him on site
All right, this isn't Sandro trying to produce a Luminium Alcross and teach us can for handball. They are the referee thinking about it
And what's he gonna do here
But it's almost as if he was gonna give the penalty and then realize that last Parmas
Was still on the attack and that a chance might unfold. Half is the question
I had the same impression as you
Maybe there's an offside
Is there a Garcia I think who yeah, they're appealing for the handball against what does a handball by Alex Wattip here
Yeah, and then
He hits the back of our of eddie
I
Are gonna see a last man back. This is what we want to see. This is the crucial question
To answer
Again still happy to just to shield possession of the attacking third 11 dosky will chase that down but not get there
That's a loose clearance and a chance to finish it
Ferrant Torres is not just that
Another ice cold splendid finish from Barcelona
That cross by Marquez Adó let's give some love and some recognition to Rafinha 95 minutes into the game and he's still
Helping out the team defending chasing balls and that one touch pass makes the difference because
Ferrant Torres touch is too heavy. It's not a good reception
But then he makes the most of it with his left foot smashing it
Into the crossbar same as Danny Omo did to secure Barcelona
For this game
And see flick
Won't be celebrating but his team Alex are back on chop of the pile
They make knocked off
Briefly as it turns out by athletic overdrip
The rivals are opponents of the cup race semi finals on Tuesday. So that gives them an extra confidence boost
Danny Omo ending his draw and becoming the MVP
Hansi flick with a perfect reading of the game and and making those substitutions
Good game good second half of Barcelona great three points and
At this point in performance again by last time